There's only one thing I ask of you:

- Please, whatever you do, don't forget to give credit to the creator of the original Appearance Miku (ままま, アラン・スミシー).

Other than that, you are free to do whatever you want with my edited version. Feel free to use the parts I've created too, such as the hand(hair)cuffs or the cap.

= faTWave

(About the version (0.9), I want to do more with it, but I lack PMX editor skills, so I just consider the model just at 0.9)